play-bar.net 2016-11-01

# Playbar

Blisbury LLP ("Blisbury") owns and operates a number of different sites on the Web (each, a "Blisbury Site"). Blisbury is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information Blisbury may gather about individuals who visit the Blisbury Sites, how that information is used, and Blisbury's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to the Blisbury Sites, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from the Blisbury Sites.

## Anonymous User Information

Blisbury collects some anonymous information each time you visit a Blisbury Site so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with Blisbury before we can collect this anonymous information.

The Blisbury Sites do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or e-mail address, in order for you to use the Blisbury Sites. The Blisbury Sites assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited the Blisbury Site, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. Blisbury analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

## Individual User Information

From time-to-time the Blisbury Sites request information from you that may identify you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, e-mail address, shipping address, and zip code), and demographic information (such as age, gender, occupation, and household income). Blisbury will not use or disclose your individual user information except as described in this privacy policy. Blisbury collects individual user information in the following ways from different Blisbury Sites: 

## Surveys or Contests

From time to time, Blisbury may conduct surveys or contests on a Blisbury Site. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose individual user information to the Blisbury Site. Contest information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Blisbury Site. We may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests. These companies may use your personal information to help the Blisbury Site communicate with you about offers from the Blisbury Site and our marketing partners. Such third parties do not have Blisbury's permission to use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose.

## Tell-A-Friend

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about any of our sites, we ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. Blisbury will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the Blisbury Site. Blisbury does not store the information related to your friends and the one-time e-mail sent pursuant to your input will be our only contact with that person for such input.

## Correspondence

If you contact Blisbury, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your e-mail address.

## Third Party Information Gathering

The Blisbury Sites include content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy.

The Blisbury Sites contain links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that Blisbury is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Cookies

Blisbury may set and access Blisbury or partner cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that a Web site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

We use cookie and web beacon technology to track which pages on the Blisbury Sites our visitors view and which Web browsers our visitors use. We may also use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences to you within various Blisbury Sites in a way that may be linked to individual user information that you elect to share with us. We also use "action tags" to assist in delivering the cookie. These action tags allow us to compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, by embedding a random identifying number on each user's browser. Then we track where that number shows up on our site.

## Sharing

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Blisbury's or such Blisbury Site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

Blisbury Sites may use third party service providers to serve ads and e-mails on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails and use information about your visits to the Blisbury Site so that we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation.

## Mergers; Business Transitions

In the event Blisbury goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use Individually Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.
